Inventory of the G. Walter Mapp Papers 1895-1935
Earl Gregg Swem Library, College of William and Mary
- Correspondence of G. Walter Mapp, 1895-1935. (Box 1-8)
  - General Correspondence, 1895-1935. (Box 1-7)
    - General Correspondence: K-M, 1895-1935., Note: "Duplicate correspondence" refers to unsigned copies of letters by Mapp. "Original correspondence" refers to signed letters written to Mapp. (Box-folder 4:1-285)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Rev. J. D. McAllister, Richmond, Virginia, 1914., 4 items. (Box-folder 4:180)
      - Correspondence from Rev. J. R. McAllister, Cape Charles, Virginia, 1922., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:181)
      - Correspondence from J. J. McBreen, Washington, D.C., 1934., 2 items. (Box-folder 4:182)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with F. Scott McBride, Washington, D.C., 1927., 2 items. (Box-folder 4:183)
      - Correspondence from Jesse McCarter, Saluda, Virginia, 1918., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:184)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with W. W. McClevy, Richmond, Virginia, 1931., 5 items. (Box-folder 4:185)
      - Duplicate correspondence to H. K. McConnell, Gates City, Virginia, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:186)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Lloyd McCready, Onley, Virginia, 1932., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:187)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with George Lee McCready, Parksley, Virginia, 1933., 2 items. (Box-folder 4:188)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Lloyd McCready, Onley, Virginia, 1932., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:189)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with N. L. McCready, New York City, New York, 1910-1911., 6 items. (Box-folder 4:190)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Roland H. McCready, Keller, Virginia, 1933., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:191)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with George W. McDaniel, Richmond, Virginia, 1914., 2 items. (Box-folder 4:192)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Marlanna Rucker McGee, East Radford, Virginia, 1922., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:193)
      - Correspondence from J. A. McGilvray, Richmond, Virginia, 1918., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:194)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Norman McGlashan, Douglaston, New York, 1935., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:195)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with H. R. McIlwaine, State Librarian, Richmond, Virginia, 1912-1928., 7 items. (Box-folder 4:196)
      - Correspondence from Edward McIntosh, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1935., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:197)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with S. L. McKingler, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1935., 2 items. (Box-folder 4:198)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with J. S. McMaster, Jersey City, New Jersey, 1911-1918., 7 items. (Box-folder 4:199)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with A. J. McMath, Onley, Virginia, 1906., 3 items. (Box-folder 4:200)
      - Telegrams from "Mears and Mears," 1920, 1922., 2 items. (Box-folder 4:201)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with A. H. G. Mears, Keller, Virginia, 1912-1927., 6 items. (Box-folder 4:202)
      - Duplicate correspondence to A. W. Mears, Keller, Virginia, 1924., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:203)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Benjamin w. Mears, Eastville, Virginia, 1928-1934., 3 items. (Box-folder 4:204)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Cecil F. Mears, Norfolk, Virginia, 1920, 1932., 4 items. (Box-folder 4:205)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Charles B. Mears, Keller, Virginia, 1911, 1922., 6 items. (Box-folder 4:206)
      - Correspondence from E. C. Mears, Painter, Virginia, 1911., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:207A)
      - Correspondence from Edgar Mears, Richmond, Virginia, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:207B)
      - Correspondence from Mrs. G. T. Mears, 1901., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:208)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Harry E. Mears, Melfa, Virginia, 1931., 4 items. (Box-folder 4:209)
      - Duplicate correspondence to J. N. Mears, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1935., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:210)
      - Duplicate correspondence to J. T. Mears, Chincoteague, Virginia, 1920., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:211)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with James E. Mears, Bristol, Virginia; Tampa, Florida; and Harborton, Virginia, 1912-1934., 18 items. (Box-folder 4:212)
      - Duplicate correspondence to John A. Mears, Keller, Virginia, 1911., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:213)
      - Duplicate correspondence to John T. Mears, Chincoteague, Virginia, 1927., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:214)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with John W. Mears, Eastern State Asylum, Williamsburg, Virginia, 1914., 2 items. (Box-folder 4:215)
      - Correspondence from L. C. Mears, Keller, Virginia, 1926., 2 items. (Box-folder 4:216)
      - Correspondence from Mrs. Margaret S. Mears, Belle Haven, Virginia, 1911., 2 items. (Box-folder 4:217)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with O. B. Mears, Kempsville, Virginia, 1911., 2 items. (Box-folder 4:218)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Orotho F. Mears, law partner, Eastville, Virginia, 1901-1927., 19 items. (Box-folder 4:219)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Will S. Mears, Gargatha, Virginia, 1924., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:220)
      - Correspondence from J. H. Meek, Richmond, Virginia, 1922., 2 items. (Box-folder 4:221)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Charles L. Melton, Front Royal, Virginia, 1919-1924., 5 items. (Box-folder 4:222)
      - Correspondence rom Charles O. Melvin, Pocomoke City, Maryland, 1901., 6 items. (Box-folder 4:223)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Will Melvin, Accomac, Virginia, 1932-1933., 3 items. (Box-folder 4:224)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Wyndham R. Meredith, Richmond, Virginia, 1920-1921., 9 items. (Box-folder 4:225)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with F. J. Merkling, Washington, D.C., 1924., 3 items. (Box-folder 4:226)
      - Correspondence from D. M. Merritt, Chincoteague, Virginia, 1906., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:227)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Metompkin Bank and Trust Co., Bloxom, Virginia, 1932., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:228)
      - Duplicate correspondence to the Metropolitan Health Department, New York City, New York, 1932., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:229)
      - Duplicate correspondence to the Metropolitan Life Insurance Co., New York City, New York, 1934., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:230)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Lula D. Metz, Manassas, Virginia, 1925., 2 items. (Box-folder 4:231)
      - Duplicate correspondence to C. V. Meyers, Keller, Virginia, 1911., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:232)
      - Duplicate correspondence to The Michie Company, Charlottesville, Virginia, 1933., 2 items. (Box-folder 4:233)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Clarence W. Miles, Baltimore, Maryland, 1933., 1 item (Box-folder 4:234)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Harry P. Miles, Atlantic, Virginia, 1922., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:235)
      - Correspondence from Miller, Bain, Beyer, and Company, 1911., 2 items. (Box-folder 4:236)
      - Correspondence from N. E. Miller, Hodgins, Virginia, 1914., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:237)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with W. E. Miller, Hampton, Virginia, 1918., 2 items. (Box-folder 4:238)
      - Correspondence from Indie Grover Milligan, Cape Charles, Virginia, 1934., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:239)
      - Duplicate correspondence from Samuel S. Milliner, Accomac, Virginia, 1933., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:240)
      - Correspondence from H. E. Mills, Saxis, Virginia, 1911., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:241)
      - Correspondence from J. S. Mills, Onancock, Virginia, 1912, 1931., 2 items. (Box-folder 4:242)
      - Correspondence from J. T. Mills, Cappahosic, Virginia, 1918., 2 items. (Box-folder 4:243)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Morgan R. Mills, Richmond, Virginia, 1920, 1927., 15 items. (Box-folder 4:244)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with E. W. Milstead, Newport News, Virginia, 1918, 1924., 2 items. (Box-folder 4:245)
      - Duplicate correspondence to W. M. Minter, Matthews, Virginia, 1934., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:246)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with David T. Mister, Belle Haven, Virginia, 1911., 2 items. (Box-folder 4:247)
      - Duplicate correspondence to J. Douglas Mitchell, Walkerton, Virginia, 1924., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:248)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Rossel Edward Mitchell, Norfolk, Virginia, 1920., 3 items. (Box-folder 4:249)
      - Correspondence from H. Moller, Baltimore, Maryland, 1900., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:250)
      - Correspondence from Otto L. Motler, Baltimore, Maryland, 1909., 4 items. (Box-folder 4:251)
      - Correspondence from C. Lee Moar, Richmond, Virginia, 1922., 2 items. (Box-folder 4:252)
      - Correspondence with R. C. L. Moncure, 1918-1930., 98 items. (Box-folder 4:253-258)
        - Duplicate and original correspondence with R. C. L. Moncure, Richmond, Virginia, 1918., 24 items. (Box-folder 4:253)
        - Correspondence with R. C. L. Moncure, 1921-1928., 17 items. (Box-folder 4:254)
        - Correspondence with R. C. L. Moncure, 1929., 11 items. (Box-folder 4:255)
        - Correspondence with R. C. L. Moncure, 1929., 11 items. (Box-folder 4:256)
        - Correspondence with R. C. L. Moncure, March 1929., 17 items. (Box-folder 4:257)
        - Correspondence with R. C. L. Moncure, April 1929-September 1930., 18 items. (Box-folder 4:258)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Robinson Moncure, Alexandria, Virginia, 1929-1934., 5 items. (Box-folder 4:259)
      - Telegram from [?] Money, Richmond, Virginia, 1918., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:260)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Moore and McCormick, Inc., New York City, New York, 1934., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:261)
      - Correspondence from G. L. Moore, Onancock, Virginia, 1911., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:262)
      - Correspondence from Isaac D. Moore, Wachapreague, Virginia, 1931., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:263)
      - Duplicate correspondence to J. T. Moore, Princess Anne C[ourt] H[ouse], Virginia, [1911]., 1 item (Box-folder 4:264)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with R. Walton Moore, 8th District Congressman, 1925-1929., 5 items. (Box-folder 4:265)
      - Correspondence from W. S. Moore, Salisbury, Maryland, 1933., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:266)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Mr. Moorecock, Richmond, Virginia, 1933., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:267)
      - Correspondence from Francis Moorshead, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1906., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:268)
      - Correspondence from Frank A. Moorshead, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1930., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:269)
      - Correspondence from F. H. Moorshead, New Market, Virginia, 1922., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:270)
      - Correspondence from E. T. Morey, Onancock, Virginia, 1922., 2 items. (Box-folder 4:271)
      - Correspondence from Faith W. Morgna, 1922., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:272)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Arthur L. Morris, Centreville, Maryland, 1933., 2 items. (Box-folder 4:273)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with C. H. Morrisette, Richmond, Virginia, 1923., 5 items. (Box-folder 4:274)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Philip S. Mosher, Quinby, Virginia and New York City, New York, 1911, 1932., 4 items. (Box-folder 4:275)
      - Correspondence from John O. Moss, Franktown, Virginia, 1912, 1914., 2 items. (Box-folder 4:276)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Mrs. B. B. Mumford [B. B. Munford?], Richmond, Virginia, 1924., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:277)
      - Correspondence from L. E. Mumford, Cape Charles, Virginia, 1911., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:278)
      - Duplicate correspondence with Murphy's Hotel, Richmond, Virginia, 1920-1932., 6 items. (Box-folder 4:279)
      - Correspondence from Louis Murphy, Richmond, Virginia, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:280)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with M. L. Murphy, Pungoteague, Virginia, 1911, 1918., 4 items. (Box-folder 4:281)
      - Correspondence from William E. Murray, Washington, D.C., 1932., 3 items. (Box-folder 4:282)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Edwin D. Muzon, Lynchburg, Virginia, 1934., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:283)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with H. P. Myers, Charlottesville, Virginia, 1922., 2 items. (Box-folder 4:284)
      - Correspondence signed E. P. M., Savagerville, Virginia, 1911., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:285)
    - General Correspondence: N-Se, 1895-1935., Note: "Duplicate correspondence" refers to unsigned copies of letters by Mapp. "Original correspondence" refers to signed letters written to Mapp. (Box-folder 5:1-276)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Thomas Nast, New York and Florida, 1931, 1934., 2 items. (Box-folder 5:1)
      - Duplicate correspondence to the National Circulating Company, New York City, New York, 1932., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:2)
      - Duplicate correspondence to National Geographic Society, Washington, D.C., 1924, 1933., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:3)
      - Correspondence from National Grocery Company, Roanoke, Virginia, 1922., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:4)
      - Correspondence from R. E. Neely, Baltimore, Maryland, 1934., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:5A)
      - Correspondence from W. J. Nelms, Newport News, Virginia, 1914., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:5B)
      - Correspondence from E. W. Nelson, Washington, D.C., 1922., 3 items. (Box-folder 5:6)
      - Correspondence from Margaret S. Nest, Harrisonburg, Virginia, 1933., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:7)
      - Duplicate correspondence to the New Republic, Westerville, Ohio, 1914., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:8)
      - Duplicate correspondence to H. L. Newbill, Centre Cross, Virginia, 1918., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:9)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Houston Newman, Edinburg, Virginia, 1929., 3 items. (Box-folder 5:10)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with the Newport News Chamber of Commerce, 1921., 2 items. (Box-folder 5:11)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Blake T. Newton, Mantross and Hague, Virginia, 1928-1929., 2 items. (Box-folder 5:12)
      - Correspondence from William J. Newton, Norfolk, Virginia, 1911., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:13)
      - Correspondence from H. O. Nicholas, Newport News, Virginia, 1918., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:14)
      - Correspondence from H. S. Prentiss Nichols, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1900-1901., 15 items. (Box-folder 5:15)
      - Correspondence from E. L. Nicholson, Snow Hill, Maryland, 1932., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:16)
      - Correspondence from H. A. Nicholson, Creeds, Virginia, 1911., 2 items. (Box-folder 5:17)
      - Correspondence from P. J. J. Nicholaides, Washington, D.C., 1933., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:18)
      - Duplicate correspondence to E. C. Ninde, Fredericksburg, Virginia, 1918., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:19)
      - Duplicate correspondence rom Luck Nininger, Washington, D.C., 1930., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:20)
      - Duplicate correspondence to G. O. Nock, Pungoteague, Virginia, 1934., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:21)
      - Correspondence from George F. Nock, Wachapreague, Virginia, 1927., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:22)
      - Duplicate correspondence to John T. Nock, Wachapreague, Virginia, 1922., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:23)
      - Correspondence from N. W. Nock, Onancock, Virginia, 1912., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:24)
      - Correspondence from Roland R. Nock, Harborton, Virginia, 1911., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:25)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Sarah Nock, Accomac, Virginia, 1932., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:26)
      - Correspondence from W. L. Nock, Temperanceville, Virginia, 1911., 2 items. (Box-folder 5:27)
      - Correspondence from W. S. Nock, Hallwood, Virginia, 1912., 4 items. (Box-folder 5:28)
      - Correspondence with B. F. Noland, Spencer, Virginia, 1922-1929., 68 items. (Box-folder 5:29-31)
        - Duplicate and original correspondence with B. F. Noland, Spencer, Virginia, 1922-1923., 24 items. (Box-folder 5:29)
        - Correspondence with B. F. Noland, 1924., 26 items. (Box-folder 5:30)
        - Correspondence with B. N. Noland, 1925-1929., 18 items. (Box-folder 5:31)
      - Correspondence with Hunter Noland, Bassett, Virginia, 1933., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:32)
      - Correspondence rom the Norfolk and Portsmouth Baptist Union, 1920., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:33)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Norfolk and Southern Railroad Co., Norfolk, Virginia, 1935., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:34)
      - Duplicate correspondence to the Norfolk and Western Railway Company, 1928, 1934., 2 items. (Box-folder 5:35)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Charles T. Norman, Richmond, Virginia, 1933-1934., 2 items. (Box-folder 5:36)
      - Duplicate correspondence to A. Lanfear Norrie, New York City, New York, n.d., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:37)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Claude L. Northam, Onancock, Virginia, 1924-1934., 5 items. (Box-folder 5:38)
      - Correspondence from J. D. Northam, Keller, Virginia, 1911., 2 items. (Box-folder 5:39)
      - Duplicate correspondence to the Northern Neck News, Warsaw, Virginia, 1918., 3 items. (Box-folder 5:40)
      - Duplicate correspondence to the Northumberland Echo, Heathsville, Virginia, 1918., 2 items. (Box-folder 5:41)
      - Correspondence from A. M. Nottingham, Onancock, Virginia, 1906., 2 items. (Box-folder 5:42)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Mrs. C. M. Nottingham, Norfolk, Virginia, 1922., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:43)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with John E. Nottingham, Franktown, Virginia, 1920-1931., 6 items. (Box-folder 5:44)
      - Correspondence from John R. Nottingham, 1911., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:45)
      - Correspondence from J. S. Nottingham, Cape Charles, Virginia, 1911., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:46)
      - Correspondence from L. L. Nottingham, Chesapeake, Virginia, 1911., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:47)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Scotia W. Nottingham, Norfolk, Virginia, 1922, 1928., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:48)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Severn M. Nottingham, 1929., 2 items. (Box-folder 5:49)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Thomas H. Nottingham, Keller, Virginia, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:50)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Whiteley B. Nottingham, New Windsor, Maryland, 1932., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:51)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with S. M. O'Bannon, 1932., 3 items. (Box-folder 5:52)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with D. C. O'Flaherty, Richmond, Virginia, 1928., 5 items. (Box-folder 5:53)
      - Letter to Editor signed "Old Time Democrat," [1918]., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:54)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with J. E. Old, Lynnhaven, Virginia, 1911-1922., 3 items. (Box-folder 5:55)
      - Correspondence from the Oliver Typewriter Co., Baltimore, Maryland, 1906., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:56)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Mrs. Carrie S. Oliver; Daugherty and Keller, Virginia; and Ocean City, Maryland, 1911-1935., 12 items. (Box-folder 5:57)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Edward O'Neil, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1906., 2 items. (Box-folder 5:58)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Onley Building and Supply Company, Onley, Virginia., 3 items. (Box-folder 5:59)
      - Correspondence from C. A. Orange, Exmore, Virginia, 1922., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:60)
      - Correspondence from M. L. Orebaugh, Norfolk, Virginia, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:61)
      - Duplicate correspondence to James J. Orr, Dryden, Virginia, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:62)
      - Correspondence from W. G. Otey, Bedford, Virginia, 1922., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:63)
      - Correspondence from Ben P. Owen, Richmond, Virginia, 1914., 7 items. (Box-folder 5:64)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Thomas W. Ozlin, Richmond, Virginia, 1928-1929., 10 items. (Box-folder 5:65)
      - Correspondence from W. T. Pace, Franklin, Virginia, 1922., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:66)
      - Correspondence from Thomas Nelson Page, Richmond, Virginia, 1912., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:67)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Edwin C. Palmer, Emporia, Virginia, 1931., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:68)
      - Correspondence from H. E. Palmer, Berlin, Maryland, 1933., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:69)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with George Parker, Blackstone, Virginia, 1925-1926., 2 items. (Box-folder 5:70)
      - Correspondence from Katherine Parker, Onancock, Virginia, 1923., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:71)
      - Correspondence from O. L. Parker, Onancock, Virginia, 1906-1914., 4 items. (Box-folder 5:72)
      - Duplicate correspondence to R. B. Parker, White Sulpher Springs, West Virginia, 1931., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:73)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with William A. Parker, Forest, Virginia, 1921., 2 items. (Box-folder 5:74)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with W. J. Parker, Mount Landing, Virginia, 1918., 3 items. (Box-folder 5:75)
      - Duplicate correspondence to R. Carlisle Parkes, Parksley, Virginia, 1932., 2 items. (Box-folder 5:76)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Mr. and Mrs. R. L. Parkes, Parksley, Virginia, 1911-1924., 10 items. (Box-folder 5:77)
      - Correspondence from C. B. Parkhill, Tampa, Florida, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:78)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Arthur W. Parks, Accomac, Virginia, 1924., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:79)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Crate Parks, Parksley, Virginia, 1911., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:80)
      - Duplicate correspondence to George J. Parks, Accomac, Virginia, 1922., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:81)
      - Duplicate correspondence to George N. Parks, Pastorla, Virginia, 1927., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:82)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Tom Parks, Accomac, Virginia, 1931., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:83)
      - Duplicate correspondence to William Parks of East Parksley, Virginia, 1932., 2 items. (Box-folder 5:84)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Parole Commissioner, Baltimore, Maryland, 1934., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:85)
      - Correspondence from E. S. Parsons, Parksley, Virginia, 1911-1912., 3 items. (Box-folder 5:86)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Henry E. Parsons, Norfolk, Virginia, 1929, 1935., 4 items. (Box-folder 5:87)
      - Duplicate correspondence to John M. Parsons, Independence, Virginia, 1933., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:88)
      - Duplicate correspondence to R. A. Parsons, Cape Charles, Virginia, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:89)
      - Duplicate correspondence to W. C. Parsons, Onley, Virginia, 1927, 1931., 2 items. (Box-folder 5:90)
      - Correspondence from D. M. Pattie, Madison, Virginia, 1918., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:91)
      - Correspondence from Leslie J. Payne, Aulander, North Carolina, 1931., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:92)
      - Duplicate correspondence to R. O. Payne, London Bridge, Virginia, [1911]., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:93)
      - Correspondence from F. C. Pederson, University, Virginia, 1935., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:94)
      - Correspondence from the Peerless Candy Company, Roanoke, Virginia, 1922., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:95)
      - Duplicate correspondence to George C. Peery, Richmond, Virginia, 1934., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:96)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Emma C. Penick, Richmond, Virginia, 1931., 2 items. (Box-folder 5:97)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Paul E. Penick, Lexington, Virginia, 1925., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:98)
      - Duplicate correspondence to the Peninsula Enterprise, Accomac, Virginia, 1923-1927., 3 items. (Box-folder 5:99)
      - Duplicate correspondence to the Peninsula Transit Co., Newport News, Virginia, 1931., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:100)
      - Correspondence from Mrs. Rucker Penn, Danville, Virginia, 1922., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:101)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Robert L. Pennington, Bristol, Virginia, 1933-1934., 12 items. (Box-folder 5:102)